slotocash.com 2008-05-22

# Sloto'Cash Casino - Privacy Policy

**24/7 Customer Support** ****

(Toll Free)  
US/Canada  
Tel: 1-866-223-7034  
UK Tel: 08-08-234-4332

International:  
Tel: +5999-433-8873  

|   | 

Sloto' Cash Casino values and respects the privacy of each and every one of its members, which we safeguard through our Privacy Statement. Please take the time to read this policy and familiarize yourself with its contents. 

You should read this notice in conjunction with the Terms of Use for this website. 

This website www.slotocash.com (the �Site�) is operated by, and information collected from this Site is collected by, Sloto'Cash., a registered business name of Deckmedia N.V, a company incorporated and based in Curacao (�Sloto' Cash �, �us� or �we�). 

## Acceptance of Privacy Policy

If you use the Site, you are accepting the terms and conditions of this Privacy Policy, and Sloto' Cash Casino will have the right to use your information as described in this Privacy Policy. If you do not agree to have your information used in any of the ways described in this Privacy Policy, you must discontinue use of the Site. We reserve the right to modify this Privacy Policy at any time. Your continued use of the Site, after we either personally notify you or generally post changes on the Site, will constitute your acceptance of those changes. 

### Personal Information Collection 

We collect personal information when you use our online gambling services, make customer enquiries, register for information or other services, or when you respond to communications from us (such as questionnaires or surveys). Selected third parties, to whom you have chosen to disclose your personal information, may also provide us with your personal information. The types of personal information we may collect could include, for example, your name and e-mail address, home address, telephone number, debit/credit card data and lifestyle and other information collected on registration or through surveys. 

### How Your Information is Processed ("Purposes")

If you choose to provide us with personal information, your personal information will be processed for the following Purposes: to allow us to provide you with online gambling services; to process any of your requests for information; to provide customer support services; to market our services or products; to improve the content of our website; to notify you about updates to our website, software and/or services; and to support any of the intended purposes stated at the time at which your information was collected, and subject to any preferences indicated by you. 

### To Whom Your Information is Disclosed ("Recipients") 

All customer data will be treated confidential and will not be sold to others, however your information may, for the Purposes, be disclosed for processing to the following Recipients: any other companies within Deckmedia N.V. and their employees; any third party service providers who use your personal information to provide services to us; or any auditors or contractors or other advisers auditing any of Deckmedia N.V. business processes, potential purchasers or investors in any company within Deckmedia N.V.. Any processing performed by any Recipients will, where required by law, be governed by a data processing agreement in the form required by law, preserving any and all of your statutory data protection rights. 

We ensure that your information will not be disclosed to government institutions or authorities except if required by law. 

### Email Choice/Opt-out... 

Sloto' Cash may use customer contact information provided by you to send information about Sloto' Cash and the products, Services and/or Sites for which you subscribed or otherwise used or accessed, including news about product updates, contests, events, and other promotional materials. If you have given us your consent, we will also send communications for unrelated products or Services. 

Sloto' Cash provides users the opportunity to opt-out of receiving communications from Sloto' Cash when you are asked to provide information to us. In addition, Sloto' Cash gives users the option of discontinuing receipt of communications from Sloto' Cash. Instructions for discontinuing receipt of communications from Sloto' Cash will be made available with each communication from Sloto' Cash or on the related Site. 

### Cookies 

A cookie is a file containing electronic information which stored on a user's hard drive to provide information needed by the user on a regular basis. Cookies are often used to save website customizations and website login information. Sloto' Cash Casino only uses cookies for the operation of the Site. 

An IP address is a number that uniquely identifies your computer on the internet. Sloto' Cash may collect IP addresses for the purposes of system administration, security, troubleshooting, and compiling aggregate information (such as how many visitors logged on to the Site). When you visit a particular web page on the Site, our servers may log your IP address. 

We may send you a permanent cookie when you register with us. A cookie is a small file that can be placed on your computer's hard disk for record-keeping purposes. Cookies can help us to recognize you when you next visit our website, note the advertisements you click on and the other sites you enter via a link from our website. This allows us to tailor the service we provide to your preferences. We may also use the data generated from cookies to compile statistical data on your use of our website. You are not obliged to accept a cookie from us or from any other website. You can modify your browser so that it will not accept cookies. Please consult the "Help" section of your browser for instructions on how to do so correctly. However, for legitimate security reasons, we may refuse access to specific website content unless you accept the use of a cookie or similar device. 

### Advertising System 

The Sloto' Cash Casino advertising system logs IP addresses in order to supply more accurate marketing features, such as language specific banners. It does not record any e-mail addresses, so you will not receive any spam mail. 

### No Absolute Safeguards

Although we will use reasonable efforts to safeguard the privacy of your information, transmissions on the internet cannot be made absolutely secure. Accordingly, we assume no responsibility or liability for disclosure of any of your information due to errors in transmission, unauthorized third-party access or other causes beyond our reasonable control. 

### User Responsibility

Please remember that protection of your privacy begins with you. You are solely responsible for maintaining the secrecy of any account ID or password you use to register, and you should always be careful and responsible whenever disclosing information online. 

Corrections, Updates and Removal of Information If you are concerned with the accuracy of the personal information provided by you and maintained by Sloto' Cash or would like your personal information removed from Sloto' Cash's records, you may use the tools made available on the Site to update or remove such information. Sloto' Cash reserves the right to charge a reasonable fee for supplying copies of such information. If you choose to delete your personal information, you may not be able to access some areas of the Site and/or Services to which you have subscribed. We will not provide a refund for any prepaid Service which is inaccessible to you because of the deletion of your personal information. We may, however, still retain your personal information in our files to resolve disputes, to enforce our user agreement, and to comply with any and all technical and legal requirements and constraints related to the security, integrity and operation of the Site. 

### Retention 

Your personal information will not be stored for any longer period than is necessary for the purposes for which it was collected. 

### Limits of Confidentiality 

For legal reasons, Sloto' Cash Casino may be required under certain circumstances to disclose your personal information. Reasons for this may include : 1) to protect and defend our rights or property ; 2) to comply with any legal process served on us . In addition, we reserve the right to disclose your personal information, including player identification, name, physical address, billing address, e-mail and/or phone number, to third parties as we believe necessary or appropriate in connection with any investigation of fraud, intellectual property infringement, piracy or any other unlawful or prohibited activity that might expose us to legal liability . 

**Information about us  
**Sloto' Cash is part of Deckmedia N. V.   
E-Zone Vredenberg,   
Brionplein 4, Curaçao, Netherlands Antilles.

**Sloto' Cash Casino may occasionally make changes to the above Privacy Statement. Any such changes will be posted on this page and it is the sole responsibility of the player to visit this page on a regular basis in order to stay informed of the changes that may occur.**

If you have any comments or questions regarding security or privacy relating to Sloto' Cash casino and affiliated partners please contact: [support@slotocash.com](mailto:support@slotocash.com)

|
